[Music]
Hello friends, in the previous video
we compared HDFC Optima Seeker
with Stylish and asked you all
which plane is better. You
all liked the video and told us
that you liked HDFC EGO Optimus
better. In this video, friends, we will talk about
ICC Lombard's Health Advantage Apex
plane, which is another plane. This
plane was earlier a plane of Bharti Airtel, but
after the recent merger, it has now become a
plane of ICC Lombard. So let's
understand this product in detail. My
name is Abhishekam and I am Investiture.
Friends, if you have not yet subscribed to our channel,
please subscribe to
your channel so that you all keep getting the best information related to health
insurance, life insurance and mutual
funds. So,
let's talk about the product details of the record
first. Friends,
in this product, the brochure shows the minimum
submersible amount as 5 lakhs and the maximum amount as 3
crores. But friends, when we
try to purchase it online, the minimum amount
shown is 7.5 lakhs and the
eligibility is 10 lakhs.  In this product, minimum
anticipation is 91 days and maximum anticipation is 65
years. Next is room rent and this charge, no
imitation has been given in this, you are being given
insurance, next
is pre-hospitalization and post-hospitalization expenses, that is,
expenses before hospitalization and
after removal, then their Shopriya
Hospitality company is giving you insurance for 60 days
and these anticipation of post-hospitalization
expenses are being given to you,
next is community bonus, friends, if
you do not take any claim in your policy, then
after renewal the company always
increases the base of your policy by 20%,
which goes up to a maximum of 100%, let us
understand this with an example, but for example, if
you have a policy of Rs 10 lakh and if you do
not get any claim in the first year, then the company
increases your policy by 20% after the next renewal, in which case
your policy becomes worth Rs 12 lakh in the next year, so every
year whenever your claim is not made  The company
increases your base by 20%, that is,
if you do not have any claim for five years, then
your policy of Rs 10 lakh
becomes Rs 20 lakh. Even if
you have a claim tomorrow,
it does not reduce your job. Next
is the restore manufactory. If you have a
claim due to which your
base sum assured and your cumulative bonus gets
lost, then the company
restores the base sum assured again. Let us consider this as an
example, but for example, if you have a
policy of Rs 10 lakh and if
after being added to 9 plans, your base sum assured becomes Rs 20 lakh
and if tomorrow you have a claim of Rs 18 or 20 lakh
and it gets completely lost, then the
company restores the base sum assured again to Rs 10 lakh. In
this 10 lakh, that is,
if you need Rs 10 lakh again, then the
company gives you a claim of Rs 10 lakh again. The company has
not given you any condition in this.
Registration for this will be available from the day after tomorrow, and in fact, partial
registration is also available. Next is road
ambulance. In this, you have paid a maximum capping of Rs. 10,000 or
one day of sub-mandatory treatment.
Next is ambulance. If you
need to take ambulance service due to any emergency treatment, then the
company is providing you coverage for that as well.
Next is domestic hospitalization and other images
for which hospitalization is required. But
if you are taking treatment from home,
then the company is also providing you coverage for these.
Next is DK
treatment, friends,
for which hospitalization is not required, like
kidney stone treatment or
cataract operation, the company is providing you coverage for all these.
Next is
organ donor treatment. If any organ of your body
fails and you are donating an organ, then the
company is providing you coverage for that as well.
Next is AYUSH treatment, that is,
Ayurveda, Yoga, Unani, Siddha, Homeopathy. So
friends, the company is providing you coverage for all these.
Next is
Health Checkup: If you take a policy,
you become eligible for a free checkup of 0.5% of the maximum Rs. 10,000,
which is done on a
cashless basis. You have to
go to their center and your
checkup is done free as per your deposit. Next is
animal vaccination, for this also the company is
providing you coverage of Rs. 10,000. For
biotech surgery, friends, if
you are going to get any treatment related to this, then the
company is providing coverage of 50% off the deposit or maximum Rs. 10
lakh. Next
is home care for other indexes for which
you are getting treatment from home, such as
chemotherapy or dialysis, then the
company is giving you coverage of 5% off subsidy for this also, maximum Rs.
50,000. So friends, in this way we have covered the
basic features of the product. Now let's
talk about the option benefits. The first
option benefit is Claim Protector. If you take
this rider thing, then the company also provides you coverage for non-payable
items like gloves, mas BP kids etc.
Next is Protector. If you take this rider
thing, then apart from your
community bonus, the company will give you a bonus based on the
index or according to inflation, which is approximately five to six
days every
year. So this is
how we have done the option. Now let's talk about
waiting period. First, the
initial waiting period is a normal 30 days
initial waiting period. But for Disease
X and Accidental Claim, next is the
waiting period for specific diseases or those
diseases which take time to form in our body
like kidney stone,
angina, piles, cataract, for the coverage of all these, the
company has a waiting period of 2 days or
you can say three premiums.
Next is the waiting period for pre-
existing diseases, that is, those
diseases which you need to have before taking the policy
like BP, sugar, there is a complete
waiting period for all these or you can say
three premiums. So friends, this is how we have done the
waiting period. Now let's talk about
network hospitals.
Lombard has more than 7000 network
hospitals, so almost all the big hospitals
come under its network hospitals, so
you will not face any problem with their soft cashless statement.
How do you give treatment to any other region?
If you do treatment in a non-network hospital, then
submit the bill and report to the company and the company will give you your money.
Now let's talk about the premium. If I
look at the premium of a child of Rs 10 lakh, then it
comes to 213 in TA 1
and 18000 in TI 2.
Friends, this tier categorization is
not based on your location, it is based on treatment, that is,
if you
want to get treatment in Mumbai, Kolkata or Gujarat, then you should pay the premium of t1
or if you
want to get treatment in any other city, then pay the
premium of tier 2.
If you get your treatment done in tier 1 instead of tier 2, then
you have to pay a
copayment. So friends, this is how we have covered
all the things of the product. I hope
you liked the information. We have
given the brochure of policy wording in the description link of the product.  It is kept, if you want you
can do it through father, if you
already have any policy of ICC Lombard then
please share after sales
experience or claim experience
so that whenever our viewers have any ICC
policy, they should already know about the claim experience of this company,
friends, we
deal in the products of all the big health insurance companies, so
if you have any health and sun retirement
then you can contact us on the number given below,
we will try to give you the best,
if you like the video then
like, share and subscribe, thank
you very much